[
    {
        "id": "01",
        "question": "How is the hiragana 'でんとうぶんか' read in kanji?",
        "answer": "伝統文化"
    },
    {
        "id": "02",
        "question": "How is the hiragana 'ごらく' read in kanji?",
        "answer": "娯楽"
    },
    {
        "id": "03",
        "question": "How is the hiragana 'さどう' read in kanji?",
        "answer": "茶道"
    },
    {
        "id": "04",
        "question": "How is the hiragana 'おちゃ' read in kanji?",
        "answer": "お茶"
    },
    {
        "id": "05",
        "question": "How is the hiragana 'みち' read in kanji?",
        "answer": "道"
    },
    {
        "id": "06",
        "question": "How is the hiragana 'しょどう' read in kanji?",
        "answer": "書道"
    },
    {
        "id": "07",
        "question": "How is the hiragana 'かぶき' read in kanji?",
        "answer": "歌舞伎"
    },
    {
        "id": "08",
        "question": "How is the hiragana 'のう' read in kanji?",
        "answer": "能"
    },
    {
        "id": "09",
        "question": "How is the hiragana 'ぶんらく' read in kanji?",
        "answer": "文楽"
    },
    {
        "id": "10",
        "question": "How is the hiragana 'すもう' read in kanji?",
        "answer": "相撲"
    },
    {
        "id": "11",
        "question": "How is the hiragana 'じゅうどう' read in kanji?",
        "answer": "柔道"
    },
    {
        "id": "12",
        "question": "How is the hiragana 'けんどう' read in kanji?",
        "answer": "剣道"
    },
    {
        "id": "13",
        "question": "How is the hiragana 'からて' read in kanji?",
        "answer": "空手"
    },
    {
        "id": "14",
        "question": "How is the hiragana 'まんざい' read in kanji?",
        "answer": "漫才"
    },
    {
        "id": "15",
        "question": "How is the hiragana 'らくご' read in kanji?",
        "answer": "落語"
    },
    {
        "id": "16",
        "question": "How is the hiragana 'いご' read in kanji?",
        "answer": "囲碁"
    },
    {
        "id": "17",
        "question": "How is the hiragana 'しょうぎ' read in kanji?",
        "answer": "将棋"
    },
    {
        "id": "18",
        "question": "How is the hiragana 'ぼんおどり' read in kanji?",
        "answer": "盆踊り"
    },
    {
        "id": "19",
        "question": "How is the hiragana 'おどり' read in kanji?",
        "answer": "踊り"
    }
]